Finding Aid for Computing Center (University of Michigan) publications, 1965-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Technical Reports
  - No. 16. A Survey of Pictorial Data-Compression Techniques, DiGuiseppe 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 17. A Compiler for an Associative Object Machine, Ash 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 18. A Network-Variational Basis for Generalized Computer Representation of Multifreedom, Constrained, Mechanical Systems, Chace 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 19. Multiprogramming in a Small-systems Environment, Mills 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 20. Topics in Computer Communications Systems, Mills 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 21. On the Representation of Markovian Systems by Network Models, Wallace 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 22. An Implementation of the Queue Analyzer System (QAS) on the IBM 360/67, Randall, Uppal, McClain and Blinn 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 23. SELMA: A Conversational System for the Graphical Specification of Markovian Queuing Networks, Jackson 1969 (Box 18)
  - No. 24. SELCIR: Systems Engineering Laboratory Circuit-Drawing Program, Blinn 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 25. A Programming System for the Simulation of Cellular Spaces, Brender 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 26. Computer Graphics in the Dynamic Analysis of Mechanical Networks, Chace and Korybalski 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 27. The Audio Response Unit User's Guide, Smith 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 28. Data Concentrator User's Guide, Mills, DiGiuseppe and Gerstenberger 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 29. The University of Michigan Plot Description System and Related CALCOMP 780/763 Post-Processing, Fronczak 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 30. DRAWL 70: A Computer Graphics Language, Herzog and Shadko 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 31. DEC PDP-7/IBM 1800 High Speed Interface Reference Manual, Foy, Jr., Brender, Frantz and Miller, 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 32. The MAD/I Manual, Bolas, Springer and Srodawa 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 33. CAMA (Computer-Aided Mathematical Analysis): A Genera Description, Wolf 1970 (Box 18)
  - No. 33. The Display File Routines User's Guide, Wagman 1970 (Box 18)